<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fitness Plan</string>
    <string name="app_version">Version: 1.0</string>
    <string name="confirm">CONFIRM</string>
    <string name="confirming">CONFIRMING</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="about_us">True Strength is dedicated to all things health and fitness, it\'s a platform where we all can learn and grow together.</string>
    <string name="contact_name">Contact: Mike</string>
    <string name="contact_email">Email: michael.truestrength@outlook.com</string>
    <string name="contact_facebook">Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/TrueStrengthNZ/</string>
    <string name="facebook_url">https://www.facebook.com/TrueStrengthNZ/</string>
    <string name="title_plan_list">Plan List</string>
    <string name="title_plan_detail">Plan Details</string>
    <string name="title_create_plan">Create New Plan</string>
    <string name="title_exercise">Exercise Details</string>
    <string name="title_exercise_list">Day Exercises</string>
    <string name="declaimer_date">DATE: 30/05/2016</string>
    <string name="declaimer_version">VERSION: V1</string>
    <string name="declaimer_content">Before beginning any exercise or nutrition programme, consult your healthcare professional or physician to avoid the potential harm of doing any inappropriate exercises or nutrition which may affect your health.  If you think you may be suffering from any medical condition, you should seek immediate medical attention.  This is particularly true if any of the following apply to your current health status:\n

1. Chest pain or pain in the neck and/or arm\n
2. Shortness of breath\n
3. A diagnosed heart condition\n
4. Joint and/or bone problems\n
5. Currently taking cardiac and/or blood pressure medications\n
6. Have not previously been physically active\n
7. Dizziness\n
8. Obesity\n
9. Allergies to particular foods\n
10. Medical conditions that permits you from eating particular foods\n
When beginning the True Strength programme be sure to start gradually.  However, if you feel any of the symptoms listed above, stop immediately and contact your physician right away.  If you engage in this exercise programme or undertake any of the nutrition recipes as listed in this programme you understand there is the possibility of physical injury or health risks, you agree that you do so at your own risk, you assume all risks to yourself and agree to release and discharge the provider of True Strength from any and all claims or causes of action, known or unknown arising out of negligence from the provider of the True Strength Programme.</string>
</resources>
